{
    "subject": "resource/Moloya_Goswami",
    "predicate": "property/occupation",
    "object": "resource/Actor",
    "human_readable": "Moloya Goswami is an actor.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9879297018051147,
            "question": "Is Moloya Goswami an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9328179359436035,
            "question": "What type of roles has Moloya Goswami played?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9109901785850525,
            "question": "Has Moloya Goswami acted in any movies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8948569893836975,
            "question": "Are there any famous actors that Moloya Goswami has worked with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7817080616950989,
            "question": "What is Moloya Goswami known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7065309286117554,
            "question": "What profession does Moloya Goswami have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.673801839351654,
            "question": "Where is Moloya Goswami from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.668977677822113,
            "question": "Has Moloya Goswami won any awards for their acting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6155720949172974,
            "question": "Is there anything else notable about Moloya Goswami's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38793081045150757,
            "question": "What are some of Moloya Goswami's most popular works?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Moloya Goswami is an actor.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8574_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything else notable about Moloya Goswami's career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8574_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Moloya Goswami won any awards for their acting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8574_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Moloya Goswami from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8574_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8574_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple pieces of information that support the statement \"Moloya Goswami is an actor.\" For example, the document at filepath `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8574/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt` explicitly lists her as a member of the \"Assamese actors\" category. Additionally, other documents describe her roles and performances in films and theatre, further confirming her status as an actress."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}